HyungRyul Kim

Email: dev.ryulth@gmail.com Contact: 010-9455-9654

I am a backend developer who wants to create a service that parents can use easily. I enjoy applying technologies that I have not experienced to side projects. Currently, I like Java & Kotlin and Spring Framework. RDB prefers MySQL and NoSQL prefers DynamoDB.

Main technology stack: Java, Kotlin, Spring Framework, MySQL, Docker, DynamoDB

GitHub: https://github.com/Ryulth

Curriculum Vitae: https://ryulth.com/cv-ko.pdf Side Project: https://ryulth.com/side-project-ko.pdf

Always worry about side effects not happening.

Work Experience HYPERCONNECT

Nov 2019 - Present

Full-time, Seoul, Republic of Korea - https://hyperconnect.com/?lang=en

- AZAR API Team Backend Software Engineer Nov 2019
 - # Developed azar application server
 - Develop azar application feature (70million match request per one day)
 - Trouble shooting
 - # Build micro service
 - Architecture design
 - Developed common module
 - Manage micro service system
- AZAR Match Squad Team Backend Software Engineer Mar 2020

Azar Card Match User Experience Enhancement Organization Developer

NHN

Jan 2019 - June 2019

Intern, Pangyo, Republic of Korea - https://www.nhn.com/en/index.nhn

- Dooray R&D Team Backend Software Engineer Intern Jan 2019 June 2019
 - Dooray messenger and editor feature development

CNTEXTILE

Oct 2018 - Dec 2018

• Internal ERP System Developer Oct 2018 - Dec 2018

Education Kyunghee University

Mar 2013 - Feb 2020

Bachelor of Computer Science

Additional Information

Depromeet

A joint IT club established with the intention of letting designers and programmers work together productively

BOAZ

Korea's first university student association big data association club

T.G.Wing

Kyunghee University, Department of Computer Engineering, Academic Club 2016 Club President

Grand Prize at KyungHee University Hackatho

Nov 2018

n KHUTHON (2nd)

Excellence Award at KyungHee University Alg

May 2017

orithm Competition (3rd)

Competition Bronze at KyungHee University Al

May 2014

gorithm Competition (3rd)

Languages

Korean

Native

English

Conversational

• OPIC September 09, 2019

INTERMEDIATE MID 2